<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type='text/xsl' href='cphelp.xsl'?>
<!--Copyright © 2005 AmericanGreetings.com-->

<topics>
	<topic name="0" prev="8" next="1" title="Table of Contents">
		<content>
		<a href="javascript:GoToTopic('1')">What is Create &amp; Print?</a><br />
		<a href="javascript:GoToTopic('2')">What do I need to do in order to use Create &amp; Print?</a><br />
		<a href="javascript:GoToTopic('3')">Getting started - How to use Create &amp; Print</a><br />
		<a href="javascript:GoToTopic('4')">Frequently Asked Questions</a><br />
		<a href="javascript:GoToTopic('5')">Using the Creative Workspace</a><br />
		<a href="javascript:GoToTopic('7')">Browser Support</a><br />
		<a href="javascript:GoToTopic('8')">Contact us</a><br />
		<a href="javascript:GoToTopic('9')">4 by 8 Photo Card Instructions</a>
		</content>
	</topic>
	<topic name="1" prev="0" next="2" title="What is Create &amp; Print?">
		<content>
		Create &amp; Print was developed for people who like to express themselves with
		one-of-a-kind cards, notes, envelopes, invitations, and more.  Our printable
		projects are easy to design and personalize, and fun to send.<br />
		<br />
		You can:
		<br />
		<ul>
			<li>Add a photo to your projects</li>
			<li>Double-check your spelling</li>
			<li>Save your completed project so you can use it again in the future</li>
		</ul>
		Create &amp; Print helps you do all that and more!<br />
		<br />
		Whether you are celebrating a special occasion, or just keeping in touch,
		Create &amp; Print has lots of ways to help you say what's on your mind and in
		your heart.  We'll give you art and words.  You add the magic.
		</content>
	</topic>
	<topic name="2" prev="1" next="3" title="What do I need to do in order to use Create &amp; Print?">
		<content>
		<ul>
			<li>Create &amp; Print software, art and templates</li>
			<li>A personal printer</li>
			<li>Paper</li>
			<li>Your imagination</li>
		</ul>
		It's quick, easy and fun!
		</content>
	</topic>
	<topic name="3" prev="2" next="4" title="Getting started - How to use Create &amp; Print">
		<content>
		Starting at the home page of Create &amp; Print, you can browse through all of the available categories
		of projects to find one that meets your needs.
		<ol>
			<li>The left side of the page will allow you to navigate through the project design <b>categories</b>.
			Click on the category names to open and explore them.</li>
			<li>The right side of the page will show you the <b>thumbnail images</b> of various projects in that category.</li>
			<li>To see a larger <b>preview</b> of the project, click on the thumbnail image.</li>
			<li>If you would like to view more projects you can click the <b>Back</b> button to return to the thumbnails
			page, or you can just select a new category.</li>
			<li>Continue to browse until you find the right project for your needs.  Click on the <b>Personalize and Print This Project</b> link to open up
			the <b>Create &amp; Print Workspace</b>.  In the workspace, you can personalize your
			project by changing the text, adding new text messages, adding a favorite
			photo, and so much more.  Have fun!</li>
			<li>When you have completed your personalizations, click the <b>Print</b> button.  Your project will be sent to your printer.</li>
		</ol>
		<b>Tips:</b>
		<br />
		<br />
		The first time you print a note card or greeting card,
		be sure to run a <b>paper feed print test</b> in the Print window. 
		You'll only need to do this the first time you print a card and Create &amp; Print will remember your settings.
		<br />
		<br />
		All text on the Create &amp; Print greeting cards and projects can be edited to
		fit your specific need.  If you see a Floral design in Thank you that you think
		would make a great Anniversary greeting, just change the text message.  It is easy, fast and
		fun!
		</content>
	</topic>
	<topic name="4" prev="3" next="51" title="Frequently Asked Questions">
		<content>
		<a href="javascript:GoToTopic('51')">Is Create &amp; Print safe to install on my computer?</a><br />
		<a href="javascript:GoToTopic('58')">How do I change greeting card sizes?</a><br />
		<a href="javascript:GoToTopic('59')">How do I Add-A-Photo to my project?</a><br />
		<a href="javascript:GoToTopic('60')">What kind of paper is best to use with Create &amp; Print?</a><br />
		<a href="javascript:GoToTopic('61')">How does a half-fold greeting print?</a><br />
		<a href="javascript:GoToTopic('62')">How does a quarter-fold greeting print?</a><br />
		<a href="javascript:GoToTopic('63')">How many copies of my project can I print?</a><br />
		<a href="javascript:GoToTopic('64')">How do I print Envelopes?</a><br />
		</content>
	</topic>
	<topic name="5" prev="64" next="40" title="Using the Creative Workspace">
		<content>
		After you have chosen the project you want to personalize, click on the <b>Personalize
		and Print This Project</b> link and the Create &amp; Print
		Workspace window will pop up.  The Workspace is where you can
		personalize and print your greeting card or project.  You can add, delete, or
		change text and art elements.<br />
		<br />
		You can start by simply highlighting the
		project's existing text message and begin typing.  Your keystrokes will change
		the sentiment right on your screen.  You can also change the size, color,
		alignment and type of font used on your project, and add shapes or photos.<br />
		<br />
		There are many other tools available in the workspace if you wish to create a
		truly unique printed project.  Each button icon represents one of the tools in the workshop.  If you need a quick hint as to what each tool does,
		place the cursor over the tool icon.  Hold the pointer over the tool icon
		for a several seconds and the message will appear.<br />
		<a href="javascript:GoToTopic('40')">Top Toolbar</a><br />
		<a href="javascript:GoToTopic('41')">Left Toolbar</a><br />
		</content>
	</topic>
	<topic name="7" prev="41" next="8" title="Browser Support">
		<content>
		We strongly recommend you use Create &amp; Print with either Internet
		Explorer 5.5 (or higher) or Netscape 4.7x (or higher).  Create &amp; Print is not compatible with Macintosh computers,
		WebTV, Eye Opener, or Internet Appliances.
		<br />
		For Internet Explorer, go to <a target="ie" href="http://www.microsoft.com/ie">www.microsoft.com/ie</a>, then Downloads.
		<br />
		For Netscape, got to <a target="ns" href="http://www.netscape.com">www.netscape.com</a>, then browser central.
		</content>
	</topic>
	<topic name="8" prev="7" next="9" title="Contact us">
		<content>
		We are here to provide support for the site, and we're always happy to hear from our customers!<br /><br />
		<a target="email" href="http://www.americangreetings.com/customer/emailus_plugin.pd?source=hpdigital">Email us  by clicking on this link.</a>
		</content>
	</topic>
	<topic name="9" prev="8" next="0" title="4 by 8 Photo Card Instructions">
		<content>
		<a href="javascript:GoToTopic('20')">Printing</a><br />
		<a href="javascript:GoToTopic('21')">When I print 4X8 Photo Cards, nothing prints or only half of the design prints.  What do I do?</a><br />
		</content>
	</topic>
	<topic name="20" prev="9" next="21" title="Printing">
		<content>
		<ol>
			<li>Select Print in the software program.</li>
			<li>Choose your printer from the menu.</li>
			<li>Choose the Paper Feed Settings button to set the way paper feeds into the printer (right side, left side, or center).</li>
			<li>When the print test is complete, insert the Photo Cards paper and print your project.</li>
		</ol>
		NOTE: The first time you print, the application will run a paper feed print test to make sure the software works correctly with your printer. Use plain paper and follow the on-screen instructions to print the test page.<br />
		</content>
	</topic>
	<topic name="21" prev="20" next="0" title="When I print 4X8 Photo Cards, nothing prints or only half of the design prints.  What do I do?">
		<content>
		All printers feed custom sized paper differently.  In order for Create And Print to determine how to print on 4X8 Photo Cards using your printer, you need to set the Paper Feed Settings within the Print dialog box.  To do this:<br />
		<br />
		<ol>
			<li>Click <b>Paper Feed Settings</b> located within the print dialog box.</li>
			<li>Under <b>Feeds from:</b>, if the Right option is selected, then change to Left.  If the Left option is selected, then change to Right.  In other words, opposite of the way it was set when you entered the Paper Feed Settings dialog.</li>
			<li>Click OK to save changes and reprint your card.</li>
		</ol>
		</content>
	</topic>
	<topic name="40" prev="5" next="41" title="Using the Creative Workspace">
		<content>
		<h2>Top Toolbar</h2>
		<img src="./cp/help/help_print.gif" border="0" align="middle"></img> <b>Print 
			your project</b>
		Send your completed greeting or project to the printer.<br />
		<br />
		<img src="./cp/help/help_open.gif" border="0" align="middle"></img> <b>Open a saved project</b>
		Open a saved project.<br />
		<br />
		<img src="./cp/help/help_close.gif" border="0" align="middle"></img> <b>Close your project</b>
		A project can be closed from the creative workspace.<br />
		<br />
		<img src="./cp/help/help_saveas.gif" border="0" align="middle"></img> <b>Save your project to </b>
		Click to save your completed project to your hard drive.<br />
		<br />
		<img src="./cp/help/help_undo.gif" border="0" align="middle"></img> <b>Undo the last change</b>
		Click to undo your last edit.<br />
		<br />
		<img src="./cp/help/help_redo.gif" border="0" align="middle"></img> <b>Redo the last change</b>
		Click to redo your last edit.<br />
		<br />
		<img src="./cp/help/help_cut.gif" border="0" align="middle"></img> <b>Cut the selected object to the clipboard</b>
		Click to cut/remove a selected item from your project.<br />
		<br />
		<img src="./cp/help/help_copy.gif" border="0" align="middle"></img> <b>Copy the selected object to the clipboard</b>
		Click to copy a selected text or image to the clipboard.<br />
		<br />
		<img src="./cp/help/help_paste.gif" border="0" align="middle"></img> <b>Paste from the clipboard</b>
		Click to place a copy of your text or image to the clipboard.<br />
		<br />
		<img src="./cp/help/help_delete.gif" border="0" align="middle"></img> <b>Delete the selected object</b>
		Click to remove a selected text or image from your project.<br />
		<br />
		<img src="./cp/help/help_spellcheck.gif" border="0" align="middle"></img> <b>Check Spelling</b>
		Click to check all spelling in the text boxes.<br />
		<br />
		<img src="./cp/help/help_grid.gif" border="0" align="middle"></img> <b>Show and hide the alignment Grid</b>
		Click to show or hide a grid that can be used for aligning text and images on 
		your project.<br />
		<br />
		<img src="./cp/help/help_extras.gif" border="0" align="middle"></img> <b>Access the Extras</b>
		Click to download fonts and spell check.<br />
		</content>
	</topic>
	<topic name="41" prev="40" next="7" title="Using the Creative Workspace">
		<content>
		<h2>Left Toolbar</h2>
		<img src="./cp/help/help_help.gif" border="0" align="middle"></img> <b>Get Help</b>
		Click to display Help<br />
		<br />
		<img src="./cp/help/help_addtextbox.gif" border="0" align="middle"></img> <b>Add a Text Box object</b>
		Click to add a text box to your greeting or project.<br />
		<br />
		<img src="./cp/help/help_addphoto.gif" border="0" align="middle"></img> <b>Add-A-Photo 
			object</b>
		Click to add a photo or art image to your greeting or project.<br />
		<br />
		<img src="./cp/help/help_addshape.gif" border="0" align="middle"></img> <b>Add a Shape object</b>
		Click to add a shape to your greeting or project.<br />
		<br />
		<img src="./cp/help/help_zoom.gif" border="0" align="middle"></img> <b>Change the Zoom level</b>
		Allows you to zoom in or out of your project.<br />
		<br />
		<img src="./cp/help/help_transform.gif" border="0" align="middle"></img> <b>Move or Size the selected object</b>
		Move, resize or rotate your selected text or image.<br />
		<br />
		<img src="./cp/help/help_flip.gif" border="0" align="middle"></img> <b>Flip the selected object</b>
		Flip your image or text from left to right or top to bottom on your project.<br />
		<br />
		<img src="./cp/help/help_rotate.gif" border="0" align="middle"></img> <b>Rotate the selected object</b>
		Click to rotate your text or image clockwise or counter clockwise.<br />
		<br />
		<img src="./cp/help/help_position.gif" border="0" align="middle"></img> <b>Change the Position of the selected object</b>
		Move selected text or image to various points on your project.<br />
		<br />
		<img src="./cp/help/help_layers.gif" border="0" align="middle"></img> <b>Change the Layering of the selected object</b>
		Move selected text or image from front to back or back to front.<br />
		<br />
		<img src="./cp/help/help_select.gif" border="0" align="middle"></img> <b>Select an object</b>
		Click to select the next or previous object within your project.<br />
		<br />
		</content>
	</topic>
	<topic name="51" prev="4" next="58" title="Is Create &amp; Print safe to install on my computer?">
		<content>
		Yes.  The Create &amp; Print software is developed by <b>AmericanGreetings.com</b> and is guaranteed to be safe from any virus.
		</content>
	</topic>
	<topic name="58" prev="51" next="59" title="How do I change greeting card sizes?">
		<content>
		All greeting cards can be printed as ½-fold or ¼-fold.  This 
			is done within the print dialog box.
		<br />
		<ol>
			<li>Complete your project and click the <b>Print</b> button.</li>
			<li>The print dialog box will appear.  In the lower left corner, click on either <b>Half-fold</b> or <b>Quarter-fold</b>
			to indicate what size greeting card you would like to print.</li>
			<li>Click the <b>OK</b> button and your project will be sent to your printer for printing.</li>
		</ol>
		</content>
	</topic>
	<topic name="59" prev="58" next="60" title="How do I Add-A-Photo to my project?">
		<content>
		You can add a photo to any Create &amp; Print project.  Some projects are 
		specifically designed as Add-A-Photo projects, with a space for your photo 
		incorporated into the project layout.  But photos can be added to all projects.  You
		just need to decide where to feature the photo.<br />
		<br />
		<b>Add-A-Photo projects:<br />
		</b>
		<br />
		If you have chosen a project that incorporates the Add-A-Photo feature in its 
		design, you can simply double-click on the words <b>"Double-Click to Add-A-Photo®"</b> to place an image
		within the card or project.<br />
		<br />
		The Add-A-Photo dialog box will open.  Browse your hard drive for the photo 
		you would like to attach to the project.  When you have found it, click the <b>Open</b> button.  The
		picture will insert itself into he designed location.<br />
		<br />
		<b>All Projects:<br />
		</b>
		<br />
		Click on the <b>Photo</b> button located in the left hand tool bar.  The Add-A-Photo 
		dialog box will open and you can browse your hard drive to find a photo.  When you 
		find the one you want, click the <b>Open</b> button.  The photo will be dropped in the center of the 
		project.  Double-click on the inserted photo to move it anywhere on the
		project, or to resize it.<br />
		<br />
		<b>Resizing and moving photos:<br />
		</b>
		<br />
		To resize a photo, click the photo to select it, and then drag the handles in any direction to make the photo the size you would like.  
		Dragging the photo by the corners will maintain the aspect ratio and will not distort the image.<br />
		<br />
		To move a photo, click and drag it from any point within the photo and move it to a different location.  Use the arrow keys on the keboard to "tweak" the location by a very small amount.<br />
		</content>
	</topic>
	<topic name="60" prev="59" next="61" title="What kind of paper is best to use with Create &amp; Print?">
		<content>
		Greeting card stock is generally best, and is available at most office supply
		stores and many department stores.  Card stock is comparable to store-bought
		card quality, and is pre-scored to make folding easier.  But any high quality,
		heavyweight paper is also great for your Create &amp; Print projects.
		</content>
	</topic>
	<topic name="61" prev="60" next="62" title="How does a half-fold greeting print?">
		<content>
		Half-fold greetings print on both sides of the paper.  You will have to 
		reinsert the paper to print on both sides.  After Create &amp; Print has checked 
		to see what type of printer you have, it may need to run a <b>paper feed print test</b> using a single 
		sheet of plain paper.  Next, a series of dialog boxes will give you the exact instructions 
		specific to your printer.  Simply follow the instructions, click the <b>Next</b> 
		button when prompted, and you will have no difficulty printing your greetings.
		</content>
	</topic>
	<topic name="62" prev="61" next="63" title="How does a quarter-fold greeting print?">
		<content>
		Quarter-fold greetings print with all of the art and text on one side of the 
		paper.  After you have printed your card, just fold the paper in half twice, and your greeting will be finished!
		</content>
	</topic>
	<topic name="63" prev="62" next="64" title="How many copies of my project can I print?">
		<content>
		You can print as many copies as you like.  This feature can be especially 
		helpful when you are printing invitations, newsletters, labels, envelopes, or 
		announcements.  Look for the <b>Number of copies</b> field in the <b>Print dialog box</b>.
		</content>
	</topic>
	<topic name="64" prev="63" next="5" title="How do I print Envelopes?">
		<content>
		Create &amp; Print includes an envelope wizard to set up and print envelopes. Follow the on-screen instructions to personalize the envelopes. Print the envelopes the same way you print a card; it should not require any special print setup.<br />
		<br />
		All envelopes are categorized by size.  ½-fold envelopes are the correct size for 
		½-fold greeting cards, ¼-fold envelopes fit the ¼-fold cards and Stationery 
		Envelopes are designed for the #10 business envelop.  Currently you cannot print 
		a ½-fold size envelope with a ¼-fold envelope design.<br />
		To specify how your printer will print the envelopes
		<br />
		<ol>
			<li>Click <b>Paper Feed Settings</b>
			located within the print dialogue box.</li>
			<li>Set the envelope position (left, center or right).</li>
			<li>Set the position of the flap (face up or face down).</li>
			<li>Set the leading edge (this is the edge that is facing the printer).</li>
			<li>Click <b>OK</b> when ready to print</li>
		</ol>
		</content>
	</topic>
</topics>
